[Music]
Innovation is baked into our culture. We
encourage experimentation in the way we
do things because these technologies are
evolving so rapidly.
>> Many life is definitely an early adopter
of um multiple technologies. Being in
the cloud for already over 10 years is
definitely uh sets us apart from the
competition. We invest on cloud
technologies. We invest in generative
AI. We see the potential that it's going
to bring closer to our goal which is to
help our customer better.
>> We are a truly a global team with global
presence.
>> We're looking for high performing team
members who are not afraid to take on
new challenges.
>> My favorite part of the job is
continuous learning and growing. We are
quite flexible in terms of um our our
work arrangements out here and uh I
definitely feel the team enjoys that
aspect of working within the space as
well.
>> We encourage our colleagues to take
ownership of their development. We
support them in a variety of ways.
Manual life has multiple mentorship and
coaching programs that really focus on
developing and coaching employees.
>> For somebody who's looking for a tech or
career in manual life, I would advise
recommend of course come in with an open
mind. Don't be afraid to ask questions.
Uh make a new friend and u take on the
day as it comes.
>> If you are looking for an environment
that is inclusive, which is supported,
then this is the place for you.
>> Let's build better together.
[Music]